twitchalerts.com 2016-04-21

# Privacy Policy - TwitchAlerts - TwitchAlerts

### Lasted Updated on January 1, 2015

TwitchAlerts is fully committed to your privacy. We created this Privacy Policy to help protect your information and assure you that it’s only being used to provide you with the highest quality of services. We value your trust, which is why we’re committed to providing exceptional service in a secure environment.

### The information TwitchAlerts collects

At TwitchAlerts, we’re constantly looking for ways to improve our offerings and develop new features that our users find valuable. In order to do so, we collect information to help us analyze behavior and interests so that we can continue to make TwitchAlerts better.

As a general visitor to the site, you may browse our site to find more information about our offerings. You are not required to provide us with any personally identifiable information as a visitor. However, we do automatically receive information from your browser or mobile device, including the name of the website from which you came to came to the TwitchAlerts website, as well as which website you’re going to when you leave. This information also includes the IP address of the computer/server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Service Provide name, web browser type, type of mobile device, computer operating system, pages accessed, and other similar information. We use all of this information to look at trends and to help us improve our offerings.

As a user, you maybe be required to provide us with personally identifiable information. We are the sole owners of any information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us during sign up, or that is passed through our platform as part of the user experience. We may also obtain information, including personal information, from third parties and other sources, such as information from the Twitch service through the Twitch API.

### How TwitchAlerts uses information

We use the information we receive in a variety of ways, the core of which is to improve TwitchAlerts. We may also use this information to maintain our services; to customize our service to meet your needs; to process transactions and donations; to collect fees or other charges; to verify your identity and prevent fraudulent transactions; to provide customer support; and to contact you.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new products or services and other information we believe you’d find valuable.

### When TwitchAlerts shares information

Our policy is to maintain the confidentiality of the personally identifiable information of individuals except in cases when the law requires disclosure or when we have your permission to do so. Occasionally, we may share aggregated statistics of user behavior (e.g. usage patterns, donation trends, user growth, etc.) with our partners and other interested parties. This information will never identify any individual personally or contain any personally identifiable information.

TwitchAlerts does not sell, lease, share, rent, or otherwise provide any personally identifiable information for marketing purposes to any companies or persons outside of TwitchAlerts. We may provide your personally identifiable information to service providers and affiliates that provide services in conjunction with our offerings, such as payment processors, fraud protection services, or other parties assisting in improving TwitchAlerts. Information is securely transmitted to these affiliates, and such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide their respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information. Please be aware that any personal information that you voluntarily choose to display in any public location through the use of our platform becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others.

TwitchAlerts will only disclose personally identifiable information to government officials and law enforcement agencies when it is required by law (e.g. in compliance with a subpoena or court order) or if we believe in good faith that such action is appropriate and necessary to protect and defend the rights of TwitchAlerts, or to protect the safety of TwitchAlerts users, employees, affiliates, and the general public.

In the event that TwitchAlerts or some or all assets related to our services are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign any information we have collected from users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

### Your access to and control over information

If desired, you may decline to share your personal information with TwitchAlerts, at which time we will no longer be able to provide you with a majority of the functionality of our offerings. If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information, you may contact us at support@twitchalerts.com. Please note that in order to protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making any changes to your personal information.

### Links

The TwitchAlerts website contains links to other sites that are not under our direct control. Please note that the TwitchAlerts Privacy Policy does not apply to these sites and TwitchAlerts is not responsible for, nor do we endorse, the privacy practices or the content of these sites. You should check the individual privacy policies of these sites to understand how they will utilize your personal information.

### Third-Party Providers and Do Not Track

TwitchAlerts may use third-party Web analytics services on our site, such as Google Analytics, to analyze how people use TwitchAlerts. Information collected by such technologies will be disclosed to or collected by these services providers, who use this information to evaluate your use of TwitchAlerts. You may choose to opt out of their services if you do not wish to have your information collected by them.

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web brosers. DNT is a way for users to tell websites and services that they do not want certain information about their visits collected. We currently do not recognize or respond to browser-initiated DNT signals at this time though, as the Internet industry is currently working towards accepted standardization and practices around DNT.

### Data Security

TwitchAlerts has strict security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access in order to safeguard your information. While we take precautions to protect sensitive information that’s transmitted online, we also protect your information offline . Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job, such as billing or customer service, are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/serves in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Please note that while we continually make every effort to implement safeguards to protect your personal information, the very nature of the Internet makes it impossible to guarantee the security of transmitted data. TwitchAlerts makes no warranties or representations as to the security and confidentiality of any data you transmit. Any data you transmit to TwitchAlerts is at your own risk, and we cannot guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by any breach of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

### Privacy of children

If you are under the age of 18, please make sure that you provide your personally identifiable information only after obtaining parental consent. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use or access TwitchAlerts at any time or in any manner. We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from persons under 13 years of age. If TwitchAlerts learns that personal information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected, we will take appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent of a child under 13 who has been using TwitchAlerts, please contact us at support@twitchalerts.com to have that child’s account remove and information deleted.

### Application of privacy policy

For users visiting TwitchAlerts from the European Economic Area or other non-US territories, please note that any data that passes through TwitchAlerts will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or those other non-US territories for use by TwitchAlerts and our affiliates for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. By providing data to TwitchAlerts, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries, except in the case of data transfers from the European Economic Area or Switzerland, which are covered under our EU-US and Swiss-US Safe Harbor Certifications detailed below. For users from outside the US, Switzerland, or the European Economic Area, pelase note that las in the US may not provide the same level of information protection as the laws of the user’s country of residence.

TwitchAlerts also adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. In compliance with such policies, TwitchAlerts is committed to addressing and resolving any complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. For all inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, including European Union or Swiss citizens, please first contact TwitchAlerts at support@twitchalerts.com.

### How TwitchAlerts uses cookies

Like many other sites on the Internet, TwitchAlerts uses cookies—small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters. TwitchAlerts uses cookies and collects IP addresses and other automatically collected information in order to better facilitate the services provided to you, and to collect non-personal aggregate data for marketing and research purposes. If you accept the cookies used on our site, we may be able to identify your system by reading the cookie stored on your system, but we will not be able to identify you unless you’ve entered your personal information.

We may also allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information from you when you visit our website or use our services.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make significant changes to this policy, we may notify you through a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine at our discretion. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at support@twitchalerts.com.

### Contact Information

Questions about the TwitchAlerts Privacy Policy can be sent to support@twitchalerts.com.
